- [Announcer] "Mystery
Science Theater 3000,"
show 504, reel one.
♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday AD ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ When the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Pan left ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Hi, girl ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ What a cool guy ♪
♪ Crow ♪
♪ He's a wisecracker ♪
♪ You're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself ♪
♪ It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
- Yes. (laughs)
- Okay, Tommer, looks
like he's ready to roll.
Why don't you go get Joel?
- Okay, hey Joel!
- Criminy, Servo, I
could've done that.
- Hi, one and all, welcome
to the satellite of Love.
Hey fellas, what up?
- Oh, we only built
the most sophisticated
robotistical invention ever!
- Yeah, his name is Minsky.
Now just push that button on
the top, Joel, to fire him up.
- All right.
(siren wailing)
- Ooh, yes.
Get this, get this, get this.
Here it comes.
- [Minsky] I am the
atomic-powered robot.
Please give my best
wishes to everybody.
- Oh, that's nice.
I imagine it's just one of the
really neat things he does,
right?
- What do ya mean?
- [Minsky] I am the
atomic-powered robot.
Please give my best
wishes to everybody.
- Huh?
- Oh, I get it.
You installed that
annoying phrase
to balance out the truly
cool things he does, right?
- No, it just does
the friendly voice.
- Yeah, we thought
it kinda distills
our own lives quite well.
- Wait, here it comes again.
- Yeah, wait.
- [Minsky] I am the
atomic-powered robot.
Please give my best
wishes to everybody.
- [Announcer] 15 seconds
to commercial sign
and keep that thing
outta my hair.
- Okay.
- [Minsky] I am the
atomic-powered robot.
Please give my best
wishes to everybody.
- Guys, do you think we
could turn that off now?
I'm kinda getting a headache.
- Nope, he's a new form of life,
and he doesn't
have an off switch.
- It's yours now, Joel,
to steward, to nurture.
- I love doin' good
things for people.
- Oh, me too.
- Oh, yeah.
- We'll be right back.
- He has your eyes.
- I am
the atomic-powered robot
- He has your head.
- Oh, he does.
- Yeah.
- Nice blueprint on him.
- [Crow And Tom] Cool.
- Really sweet.
(upbeat music)
- So I think he was just,
how are you two
gettin' along in here?
Hey, did see what he--
- Nothing, no.
- Oh, you were too.
- No.
- Joel.
- Nancy and Sluggo
are calling on the--
- Stay away from my--
- Oh!
- Oh, hi, Joel.
That was really
something. (chuckles)
Well, anyway, Dr. Forrester's
been away since last Tuesday.
I finally convinced him to go
to one of his class reunions.
He's got nothin'
to be ashamed of.
So I've taken it upon myself
to develop this week's
invention exchange.
Now, we've all heard of
virtual reality, right,
the gloves, the
goggles, the wires?
Well, I've come up
with a similar concept
that allows the average person
to acheive that universal goal,
becoming a stand-up comedian.
It actually puts you
inside the total
comedy club environment
with the laughter,
the clinking glasses,
the waitresses, the
overpriced drinks.
It's something I like
to call virtual comedy.
And I think it just might go
a little something like this.
(machine clicking)
(audience laughing)
- Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
You guys are a great crowd.
Oh, thanks for
comin' out tonight.
Well, what can I tell
you about myself?
Well, I'm single. (chuckles)
Big surprise there,
huh? (laughs)
(audience laughing)
Oh, thanks, you guys are great.
Give yourselves a round
of applause for comin' out
and supportin'
live comedy, yeah.
- All this adulation
can't be too good for Frank.
- All right, okay.
- Let's see how he deals with
a couple of drunken hecklers.
- Oh, what else?
Oh, well, I went
to visit my mother.
That's always a
good thing to do.
On the way there,
I gut pulled over
by some cops.
- You suck.
- God, I hate the, huh?
- [Heckler] You're not funny.
- Well, you're, duh,
pretty ugly is what you are.
Huh, huh?
(audience jeering)
- Boo!
- You suck.
- Well, I--
- You're terrible.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to--
- You're not funny.
- Imply that--
- It's almost too easy.
- I don't think this--
- Your turn, Joel.
- I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna bring out your
headliner right now.
- Boo.
- Get off the stage.
- Well, sirs, we've all
played miniature golf
into the small hours,
and it presents quite a
few nagging questions.
- Like, is it really golf?
- No, it's not.
- And is it really miniature?
- Oh, not at all.
It takes up a heck
of a lot of space.
- Hence this week's invention.
Not only have we taken golf
and turned it
truly microscopic--
- [Crow] Witness the microscope.
- But micro-golf really
is actually golf.
Here's how it works.
On each of these slides
is an entire golf course
combining the technical know-how
of biologists like
Alexander Fleming
with the impeccable course
design acumen of Jack Nicklaus
and Chi Chi Rodriguez.
- Huh?
- Hey, each course
is constructed
of lush E. coli
partimen specimen.
And the finest
subcutaneous fascia.
- Okay, now I use
this paramecium for
a seven iron, right?
- Right, Joel.
But I'd consider the euglena
niblick on this shot.
And try to put some spin on it.
- All right.
- In keeping with
the grandeur of micro-golf,
let us speak in hushed tones.
- All right, and (grunts).
- Robinson teed off moments
ago on the short par-five 11th,
normally considered
a birdie hole.
He really let fly using a
medium-shafted mitochondria.
His Golgi body is sitting a
neat 0.07 micromillimeters
from the flag.
- Robinson really
needs a birdie,
because the wheels
have been coming off.
- This shot is a bit
trickier than it looks,
what with the lymphatic
plasma to the left
and the green sloping
towards the nucleoli.
- All right, I'm linin' the
pernicious anemia culture.
I'm gonna use my pitching
wedge to loft it.
- Oh, the wheels
really are coming off.
(Joel groans)
- There they go.
- What do ya think, sirs?
(audience jeering)
- All in all,
I'm glad I went, Frank.
I think I came off rather well.
- I didn't mean
anything by that.
Actually, your wife
is very lovely, sir.
Now please sit down, it
was all in good humor.
You're a really nice audience.
Bouncer, is there a bouncer?
- Frank really does stink,
you know?
Anyway, Joel, your
experiment this week
has a duel purpose.
- Security.
(Frank speaks faintly)
- So it'll hurt like always,
but my little trip to the
alma mater reminded me
that I had done
some undergrad study--
- Please, please, no.
- In the field--
- Stand back.
- Of super-villainry.
- I just wanted share.
- I'll be conducting
a little seminar--
- It's all in good fun.
- After the film,
taking some questions.
(Frank speaking faintly)
- In the meantime--
- No, no, please.
Please enjoy "Secret
Agent Super Dragon."
- Security, security!
No, no, no, ah.
(audience jeering)
- [All] Shh.
- Joel's teeing off.
- 0.004!
(buzzer sounding)
(all shouting chaotically)
- [Joel] I can't make this hole.
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
(tense dramatic music)
Hey, it looks kind of like a
Mickey Spillane still-life.
- Oh, oh, it's called
Secret Agent, hey, hey.
- Dig the tunes.
- One of these things
is not like the other.
One of these things just, oh.
- Someone left a crayon burning.
I hate that.
- Yeah, me too.
It smells.
- By special arrangement?
What, did they have to get
her out of the fourth grade?
- Yep.
(phone ringing)
Sir, you have a call
on chamber four.
(Tom humming)
And of course,
Technicolor as himself.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm. (chuckles)
- (coughs) You know,
I'm gonna sue this movie
for secondhand smoke.
(Tom humming)
- Suggested by?
Hey, why don't you guys
write a screenplay,
but give me credit for it, okay?
- Boy, I bet the hero of
this film is really cool.
He smokes and carries a gun
and makes a lot of phone calls.
(tires squealing)
- Brought to you by Firestone.
- Where the rubber
meets the road.
(all imitating fly buzzing)
- Help me.
(curious music)
Ooh, what?
Oh, oh, J. Edgar
Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoover.
- (chuckles) Secret
Agent Mary Kay.
- Oh, man, she doesn't
have any blush.
Just forget it.
(Tom groans)
- Oh, damn these things.
Which key is it?
I can never remember,
I've got too many.
I have to get rid of
a couple of these.
(all imitating alarm beeping)
- (chuckles) Oh, watch this.
They're gonna pan up,
it's gonna be John Cleese.
- Right.
- Say.
- You know, eventually,
this is gonna get annoying.
- Eventually?
- Well.
(music grows tense)
- Oh, no, it's a Hercules film.
(Crow harmonizing)
- I hope that's not the Secret
Agent Dragon down there.
- Hey, who pulled William
Holden out of the pool?
- Glad they did.
- Oh, you can tell
by the lawn furniture
that he's a secret agent.
- No, she's gonna open letters!
- We now return
to "I, Claudius."
- Oh, that's more pink
than I would ever wear.
- [Tom] Mm, mm-hmm.
- Well, he's done on
that side. (giggles)
- Hey.
Look how far you can
see into his nose.
- Secret Agent Super Booger.
(metronome ticking)
- Pepper, you're
goin' undercover.
- Oh, no, Madame
Sousatzka was here.
- Hey, I hope she's
speedin' up the film.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Joey Heatherton.
(Joel imitating crowd cheering)
- [All] Huh?
(all humming "The Stripper")
- What is this, a Bergman film?
(mysterious music)
- It's 10:30, do you know
where your hot chick is?
- Oh, I gotta remember
to write that dream down.
- Wait a minute, I'm Scott Baio!
- Oh, buffalo shot,
sorry about that.
- Comfort.
How'd you ever
find me here, huh?
- (giggles) Do your horrible
yoga exercises permit you
to kiss me?
- Oh, not exactly.
This is for Comfort.
And this--
(Comfort gasps)
- Is for Grandma.
- Let me go!
- Is for Edwin's pool.
- [Comfort] Bryan! (screams)
- Boy, relationships
with secretaries
were a lot different back then.
- Already I'm a dickweed.
- Hey, got any gum?
- That's a nice way to--
(audio warbles)
Come on, pull me outta
here, you big oaf.
I'm not Agent Fulton.
I'm not on duty.
- Ow, ow!
- Then why'd you come
more than prepared?
The boss sent you,
didn't he, huh?
Hmm, hmm?
- Hmm, hmm?
- No, Coleman didn't send me.
It was my idea.
I thought you'd be
pleased to see me,
but I see I was wrong.
- Come on, tell, why
did you come, really?
- I thought you were Matt Helm.
- All right, Coleman did
send me on an assignment.
We need Super Dragon.
- Oh, no, no.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Super Dragon
no longer exists.
- The Popeye, yeah. (mutters)
- I'm just plain
Bryan Cooper now.
But I'm listening.
Go ahead.
- Have you ever heard
of Fremont, Michigan?
- [Bryan] Yeah, it's a little
college town, isn't it?
- That's right, just an
ordinary college town
'til strange things
started to happen.
- [Bryan] Like what?
- Two healthy students
students suddenly die
of heart failure.
- Oh, I've heard this one.
- Four others strangely collapse
from an unknown
nervous disorder.
Fights break out for no reason.
and no one can explain
how all this insanity
has overtaken the
whole student body.
- It's college, lighten up.
- The doctors and police
don't have any connections.
But Coleman smells
something burning.
- Well, they make stoves,
I mean, oh.
- And he wants me
to put out the fire,
well, not on your life.
I got my fireman suit hangin'
up in the closet there.
- You could cancel
your resignation.
- Not on your life.
- He has no batch,
he's perfectly smooth.
- Wow.
- (gasps) Really?
- That's the story,
except for Agent Wilson,
who was sent to investigate.
- Mm-hmm.
- He was found dead
after four days
at the bottom of
an elevator shaft.
(all imitating "Shaft" theme)
- Jackson.
Come on, you've worked
with me for 10 years.
If anything's wrong in Fremont,
he should be able to handle it.
Don't you worry about it.
(walkie buzzing)
- No, no, no, you
let me handle this.
Even Coleman hasn't
got the right
to interrupt a man's privacy.
- Oh, that's my Super Dragon.
- D'oh.
♪ Fred Winston, WLS Chicago ♪
- Hello?
- [Coleman] Oh, Cooper.
- Yes, it's me,
Bryan Cooper talking.
How are ya, I'm fine,
never felt better.
- [Coleman] Agent Fulton there?
- That's right, Agent
Fulton's right here.
But it won't do you any good.
I'm not leaving the place.
- [Coleman] Jackson's dead.
- What?
- His car plunged
into the river,
and he was killed instantly,
two or three miles
outside of Fremont.
- How are you?
- We're not convinced
it was an accident.
- If Fritz Hollings
were Supermarionation.
- You were very good friends,
and so I wanted to
tell you right away.
- Coleman?
- Hello?
- Coleman, are you there?
- Hello, hello, Mr. Coleman?
I seem cut off from yous.
Yes, hello, hello?
- Why, he hung up on me,
that son of a (chuckles).
- (sighs) I'm gonna go
lay on the lawn again.
This bites.
- Did you know about Jackson?
- How about you, huh?
- What happened to him?
- He's dead.
- Jim.
- You better get dressed.
- Bert Convy, P.I.
- I'm going to Fremont.
- Your friend's death
was an accident.
The trouble is, if one
doesn't know that Canyon Road,
it can be pretty dangerous.
- But Jackson was
a very good driver.
- Sure, but folks
saw him pick up
a good-looking girl.
- Oh, look,
they're in America,
'cause there's a flag.
- I think he took his eyes
off the road for an instant.
Those things can happen.
- Who was the girl?
- Christine Bruder, a
girl from Amsterdam.
She's a friend of Mr. Ross,
who owns a bowling alley
on Marlboro Street.
- Oh, where the flavor is.
- But her body wasn't found.
- That's a little
strange, don't you think?
- [Officer] Not at all, it was
probably washed downstream.
- I wonder if he's smooth, too.
- That's a brilliant
explanation.
- This is everything
Jackson had with him.
- (chuckles) Personal effects
make me happy.
- These are the keys
to his apartment.
I know my job, eh? (laughs)
- I hope you're
saving your money.
- Well, sure, I've
got a six-month CED
and an IR, hey, hey.
(suspenseful music)
(Tom humming)
- Hi, honey, I'm smooth.
- Cato?
Yes, my little friend. (mumbles)
- Oh, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
- Hmm, wait a minute, I
broke into my own place.
- Well, that's a weird switch.
- Light doesn't travel
as fast in his world.
- Heh, now it's time
for my kooky slides.
- [Crow] Hmm?
- Oh, this is before
they had Post-it notes.
- Oh.
This is gonna be
even more private
than I thought. (chuckles)
- He's got DNA up on the wall.
- It's time for the
Banana Splits show!
(cuckoo clock chirping)
- I'm cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs!
Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs, woo-hoo!
- Oh, and a beer back.
Oh, wait, man, this is
like "Pee-wee's Playhouse."
- Congratulations
on your purchase
of a Black Forest cuckoo clock.
(upbeat music)
- Ross Perot, the early years.
- [Bryan] Ross.
- It is Ross!
- I hope you're not in
any hurry to close up.
I'd like to have a few words
with you.
- What do you want?
Let me go.
- I want a Snickers, now.
- There's only $10
in the cash drawer.
- I don't want any money.
I'll settle for about less than
that, just some of this gum,
and not this stuff either, but
the stuff you give to kids.
Stay there.
That a boy.
- But I've got a Charlie Callas
audition to go-ho-ho-ho to.
- What's so special about this?
- Nothin', it's just a
different brand, that's all.
Oh!
(slap cracking)
- I don't believe you.
- Ooh, you're workin'
for the Wrigley
company, aren't you?
Now let's talk some more.
What do you know about
Christine Bruder?
- She chews Juicy Fruit, okay?
What do you want from me?
- I don't know anything.
She came here from
Amsterdam about a yeah ago.
And now she's--
- And now she's dead.
- Yes.
- Yes, yes.
- Do you believe that?
- Um, no.
- Why not?
(slap cracking)
- Yes!
- I don't believe that either.
- Don't hit my sore ear again,
Mr. Gower.
- Would you like a stick
of chewing gum?
- Please.
- Hmm?
- No.
Please don't.
- Go ahead and take it.
- No, no, no, no!
- I've got dental work!
- Chew it.
Chew it.
- It's funny joke garlic gum.
- All right, I'll
tell you about her.
- All right.
Let's see what you
have to say, huh.
- She came from Amsterdam.
And I met her.
(tires squealing)
- Duck!
- Oh!
(guns banging)
- It was P.K. Wrigley himself.
- A drive-by snack bar assault.
- I think you should talk
to your delivery man.
- Twin Peaks.
(curious music)
- Huh, slapped him
a little too hard.
- Oh, delicious fruit flavor
burst right through his skull.
- Tonight, who wants gum?
- He did, he did.
(Tom humming)
- The thin blue lines.
- Right above the
massage parlor, huh?
- That's convenient.
Oh, I get it, he's
an undercover agent
for the Apartment Guide.
- [Joel] Get that wind
ensemble outta here.
- Hello, yeah, nice,
but not my color.
Have you got it in salmon pink?
Mm.
Hmm.
- Well, what do ya, super neat,
he's got a puppet stage
right here in his room.
- [Joel] Mm, this place is
nook crazy, I don't know.
- Dust, need to get
Hazel in here to clean.
(laid-back bass-heavy music)
♪ Diamonds on my windshield
and these tears from heaven ♪
♪ I'm rollin' into town
on the interstate ♪
- [Joel] Only to
find Gideon's Bible.
(suspenseful music)
- I may be a secret agent,
but there are places
even I won't look.
- (chuckles) I'll
just take this.
I take one thing from each
apartment I break into.
I figure that's fair.
- Andre Gregory, but why?
- Should be Wally
Shawn on the other one.
- Oh, so that's where he
keeps his aunt and uncle, huh.
- I know Ron Carter's
around here somewhere.
(tense music)
- Hello, Uhura.
(guns banging)
- [Joel] Quick, get
it under cold water!
- You've been
eatin' French fries
with Morrie Moskovitch,
haven't you?
- Oh, he didn't flush.
- Ooh.
- [Joel] I hope
you're satisfied.
Geez, that hurts.
- Shot him with a knife.
Oh, this car has a neat
pasta maker option.
(phone buzzing)
- It's Walter Winchell.
- Yes, what is it?
- [Bryan] It's me, Super Dragon.
- Super Dragon who?
- How did you enjoy your trip?
- Well, they gave
me a warm welcome.
I've made my mind up.
- I'm gonna keep my baby.
- I'm gonna take
Jackson's assignment.
I'll need an assistant.
How about Baby Face?
- Baby Face?
- But he's three.
- You want a gangster?
But he's in Sing
Sing serving time
on a sentence as big
as an encyclopedia.
- Well, that means
he knows a lot.
Get him out.
- It's impossible.
- Ah, got it all tangled up.
- Analyze it?
There's absolutely nothing
in that stick of chewing gum.
Our scientists haven't been able
to find the smallest
trace of drug in it.
- But it just bothers me,
that's all, it's just--
- If there is one, it's
tasteless, odorless,
and leaves no trace
in the human body.
- Velveeta?
- How many have taken
a dose of this poison
without knowing it?
And why is the drug being
handed out among miners?
Cooper, why is the drug
being circulated gratis?
That's what I wanna know.
There's no profit in it.
There must be an
ulterior motive.
- Is this part of my review?
- That's what we've
got to find out.
What is it?
And who are the distributors?
What are they after?
- Delicious fruit flavor, sir?
- I don't know that yet.
But it must be pretty important
if they're willing to leave
behind them a string of corpses.
We have one clue,
Christine Bruder,
and she seems to have escaped.
All the import documents,
all the Ming vases
found in Ross's room,
they all seem to
point to one city.
- Circle Pines.
- Amsterdam.
- Oh.
- Going to leave?
- Now.
(toy warbling)
- From the line of Secret
Agent Super Dragon toys!
- Andy Devine.
- Baby!
- Here I am.
- [Bryan] Baby,
you old war horse,
how are ya, huh? (chuckles)
- A brother's touch.
- Hey, you're getting
a little tired
of living upstate,
aren't ya, huh?
- You know how it is.
You go soft up in Sing Sing.
I need a vacation.
- Things may get hot.
- It's better than bein' on ice.
- Remember, he's not
a permanent gift.
You will return him at
the end of the assignment,
and don't forget it.
- Okay.
- Good luck to both of you.
- Thanks.
- [Joel] Now, what was
our assignment again?
- Hey, speakin' of gifts.
And you don't have
to return that one.
- And you?
- I got the twin.
- They're not hot, are they?
- I built it with my own hands.
I got a patent on it.
- Mm, same pink, different day.
- Everything's inside,
passports, money,
identification of the agents
in Amsterdam.
- Sweet.
- Officially, you're a lawyer
looking for Christine Bruder
concerning an inheritance.
- Well, well done,
Agent Fulton.
- Agent Popo?
- Don't mention it.
- Do not worship
false eyelashes.
- Bryan, I had a dream.
I dreamt I was in a
field of tulips with you.
- Sometimes dreams come true.
(group shouting)
(otherworldly music)
♪ Wonderful,
wonderful Copenhagen ♪
(Tom humming)
Well, what do ya, only
the Dutch. (chuckles)
- Excuse me, do
you speak English?
- Frusen Gladje?
- Perhaps some French?
No?
- Nee.
- Italian?
- Some other time.
- Nee.
(bells chiming)
- Hey, does anybody
else hear these bells?
- You know, this town
can get pretty annoying.
- The Prisoner.
- Look, they got kind of a
weird miniature golf course
on the second floor up there.
- It's called the Family Circus,
see, Billy drew the strip.
- Boy, I sure would like
to tilt at that, huh.
(Tom chuckling)
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
(Tom harmonizing)
Look, man, I don't know, Tom.
This Secret Agent
Super Dragon music
that you turned into a song
doesn't look that
commercial to me.
- It ain't supposed to be
commercial, man, it's jazz.
- Well, how would you
describe jazz anyway, Tom?
- Oh man, if you have to
ask, you'll never know.
- Yeah, whatever.
Let's go, let's wail!
- Right, daddy.
One, a two, a one,
two, three, four.
(jazzy laid-back music)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
Take it, Crow Daddy.
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Yeah, grab on that, Joel.
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Ha, ha, look at me now.
♪ Secret Agent ♪
- Wait, wait a second.
You mean it just goes
on like that, huh?
- Crow takes a trumpet solo now.
- I only picked up the
trumpet a few minutes ago.
I only know two notes.
- Well, it's not my fault
if ya chops ain't together.
- Hey, chop in this, Pal.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a second.
- Oh, how'd you
like a marimba?
- Wait a second.
Cut it out, guys.
Listen, I've got an idea.
Just keep playin' and
singin' like you were,
and I'll add some spice.
Trust me, man.
- Okay.
From the top, babies.
(jazzy laid-back music)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Yeah, with action.
(imitates explosion)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
- Boom! (imitates gun banging)
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- With romance. (smooches)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Intrigue. (imitates
explosions booming)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- With boats. (imitates
motor rumbling)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Oh baby, baby, baby, baby.
I killed that fat back, hey.
Baby, back, baby. (harmonizes)
Oh, sorry, guys.
- Joel, man, you are
really out there.
It took courage to do
what you did, baby.
You took a risk, you stepped
out there on the cuttin' edge,
and ya failed miserably.
Now could we please do it
the way I wrote it, please?
(jazzy laid-back music)
♪ Secret Agent ♪
(Tom scatting)
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- Secret Agent Super Dragon.
- My bots are terminally hip.
- Secret Agent Super--
- But I love 'em anyway.
♪ Secret Agent ♪
- We'll be right back, man.
(Tom scatting)
♪ Super Dragon ♪
♪ Secret Agent ♪
♪ Secret Agent Super Dragon ♪
♪ Super Dragon ♪
- [Bryan] Look at it closely.
- Come on, look at it!
- No doubt about it.
- It's a photograph.
- He's been following
me for days.
- [Baby Face] Can I come in?
- What is it?
- I wanna show you
these little toys I brought.
- [Group] No!
- Oh, but if I'm in the way,
I'll come back later.
- No, no.
Stay, stay, stay.
- Introduce the bodyguard.
- Mm-hmm.
This is Baby Face.
This is Charity Farrel,
alias Rembrandt 13.
- Oh, well then, huh?
- Our man in Holland.
- Say.
- Oh, well, (laughs)
I see we're in good shape.
How are you, Charity?
Well, how are things?
- Like the country: flat.
- Well, I don't think
you'll be bored with us.
- It's a joke, forget it.
- Now tell me,
what do you know about
Christine Bruder?
- Secret Agent Super Rude,
if you ask me.
- She lives inside of Ruuklin,
number five.
- You been to see her?
- Yes, but nobody answers there.
- Porter?
- There are no
porters in Holland.
- Well, that's a
good thing to know.
- Oh, shut up, M. Emmet Walsh.
- Excuse me.
- Neighbors?
- [Charity] They
don't know anything.
- Men in her life?
- Mennonites?
- Quite a few.
- Most important?
- Lamas.
- Fernando or Lorenzo?
- Lamas is a millionaire,
mad for her.
The mask you sent me was
the one that Christine wore
at his masked ball last year.
- Good, we'll start with him.
- It's already done.
Senor Lamas is receiving
attorney Bryan Cooper
tomorrow at 10.
- Fine.
I think we'll get
along all right.
- Anything else?
- Yes, one little thing.
Are you a natural redhead?
- Are you a natural blackhead?
- You'll have to
take my word for it.
For now.
- [Joel] Wait, are you saying,
does that mean I'm, oh, bye.
- Oh, flat, I get it.
- You know what I always said.
Dames are like safes.
Some guys know their
secrets and some guys don't.
- Is that what
you've always said?
- Yeah.
- I think you spend too
much time cracking safes.
(Tom imitates jaunty music)
- Why, there's Amsterdam.
- Hey, Morey!
Oh, oh.
- [Joel] Hey, his eyes
have a zoom feature.
- I think it's time we made
a couple of social calls.
Let's start with
Christine Bruder.
- All right.
- Now, why did he
bring this guy?
- I made you an outfit
special for the occasion.
- It's a bullet-proof teddy.
- It's the coolest thing going
and absolutely bullet proof.
- This won't go
with my black skirt.
(speaking drowned out)
- Well, what did you want,
huh, buttons and bows?
- Oh, there's a satin tap
pant that goes with it.
- And while we're on
the subject of buttons,
perfect, huh?
- I should have brought
Jack Weston.
- Looks just like the others.
- He's kind of a white
trash Q, isn't he?
- Yeah.
- It's ingenious, it
closes your jacket.
- All right.
- Okay, now, I'm
the escaped convict,
and you're the warden's
wife. (chuckles)
- Perfect fit, huh?
- It's a little tight
in the bosom.
- What's this for?
- This
is a safety.
- Are they going steady now?
- That's it.
- It seems to work all right.
- Hey, now tell me
I'm not a genius.
- [Bryan] All right,
you're not a genius.
- Hey, I walked
right into that one.
- A boom.
- Oh, now he's Secret
Agent Super Loiterer.
- [Baby Face] There you are.
- Larrabee, is that you?
- Andy Capp's gained weight.
- Is it busted?
- No, it isn't.
(Tom humming)
- I know what you're
wearing. (laughs lecherously)
(curious music)
- Boy, they've seen
a lot of apartments
on this tip, haven't they?
- Hey, it's Rula Lenska's place.
- I hope this isn't
like a John Waters film
and they lick all the furniture.
- Dub Taylor on vibes.
- Hmm, Broy tans.
- Here, try opening the top.
Gimme that.
- Well, I loosened it for ya.
Oh, I didn't get you anything.
- He's wearing the
Phil Harris collection.
- Oh, no, it's
Grandma's brag book.
- Here, you keep the
picture of Vic Tayback.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] I'm just gonna
freshen up in here, okay.
♪ I enjoy being a girl ♪
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Mother Teresa.
(Crow gasps)
- Hey.
- Or maybe not.
- Are you looking for somewhere
to sleep or something else?
- [Bryan] No, I was feeling a
little bit lonely, that's all.
- Did you think I
would keep you company?
- Something like that, yes.
- Do you have a
towel I can borrow?
- That might have
been your idea,
but you've come to
the wrong address.
Give me my robe.
- Oh, sure.
- [Brunette] Stay where you are.
- Lay down.
- Would you turn your
face to the wall, please.
- Oh, no, I don't mind turning.
I like all kinds of games.
(Baby Face whistles)
- Oh, pretty lady.
(Baby Face chuckles)
(Crow chuckles)
- And who is this?
- Who, him?
Why, I never saw that
man before in my life.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
What do you think you're doing
in this nice lady's bedroom?
Why don't you get outta
here, you stupid oaf.
Get out of here.
- Oh, okay, okay.
I'm goin'.
I got the wrong door.
- Allen and Rossi,
ladies and gentlemen,
Allen and Rossi.
(Joel cheers)
- With Julie Budd.
- [Brunette] And you,
what are you waiting for?
- Well, a little information
if you don't mind.
Do you happen to
know this girl, hm?
- Why yes, it's
Christine Bruder.
She's living here with me.
What do you wanna know for?
- I happen to be a lawyer.
I'm here on a very important
inheritance problem.
My name is Bryan Cooper.
- Cooper, like the
hockey equipment.
- I'm sorry, but Christine's
not in Amsterdam.
She's away with some friends.
- Do you happen to know
when she'll be getting back?
- I imagine, if she's having
fun, it'll be a while.
- Well, I'd like
to see her someday
when she's not so
busy amusing herself.
- But please, next
time, ring the bell.
Leave me your address
in case my friend returns.
- Geez, they talk like
a "Speed Racer" cartoon.
- Sure, sure, here you are.
Hope I see you again, hmm.
- Hey, secret agent's crossed
out and lawyer's written in.
Hmm, oh well.
- You're on "Larry King Live."
Europe, you're on the air.
- Please, Alex, you've
got to listen carefully.
- Yeah, I know, I
look like Spike Jones.
- You must do it.
He's very dangerous.
That's right, just
do what I tell you.
- Go to the window.
- Yes, you must!
- Increase your bust.
- Oh, enough spy crap, time
to see Amsterdam. (chuckles)
(upbeat music)
(stately orchestral music)
- "Brideshead Revisited,"
"To the Manor Born,"
"Upstairs, Downstairs," "The
Magician," with Bill Bixby.
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- [Man] That's the last picture
of her, over a year ago.
- She has a beard now.
- Mario Cuomo?
- Christine and I
were very good friends.
- Nobody in this movie knows
when to stop decorating.
- You got any art here?
- Then all of a sudden--
- Kablooey.
- A girl I thought I knew
became a stranger,
moody, withdrawn.
I found out she'd
begun to drug herself.
I tried to get her to stop it.
She wouldn't.
She booked passage for America.
Now you say that she's returned.
- But good luck with
your pledge drive.
- I'd have expected
her to telephone.
- Wanna give this a try?
- Are you having an auction
masquerade this year?
- Yes, I wouldn't
miss it for anything.
- Except cheese.
- This year, I'm
offering a canvas
that's rather extraordinary.
You're a lover of
the arts, aren't you?
- Well, I'm afraid all
I can afford is to look.
(men laughing)
- Get out!
- May I show you my Lute
Player by Franz Hals?
- [Group] No, no, no, no, no.
- Please.
- It's the prize of
the entire collection.
- Emo, avec lute.
- It's worth over a
million Dutch florins.
But I expect it to
raise considerably more.
- Ooh.
- No, it'll all be for charity.
I think you'll find
this interesting.
- But stupid.
- Over here.
- Get in this.
- It's an international hospital
for babies with malnutrition.
- And pancakes.
- Art is a marvelous thing.
But saving lives, children's
lives, especially--
- It's not that good.
- Is more important.
That's why I always try to
make my auction spectacular.
- It appeals to
everyone's vanity.
- And Apollonia, too.
- Generosity,
as you know, is rare.
Vanity, on the other hand,
is a rather common trait.
- Yes, but the vain
like to be seen.
And your parties are
masquerades, aren't they?
(Tom chuckles)
- That makes it a
little more exciting.
The losers can remain anonymous.
- And the winners
remain bottomless.
- And when the winner
removes his mask,
there is usually applause.
And his vanity is
satisfied completely.
- Oh, that's most ingenious,
but I'm afraid we've taken up
too much of your time.
- Not at all.
I'm very grateful to
you for your visit.
- What else, oh.
- We're all anxious
to locate Christine.
I've every hope we can.
We'll keep in touch.
- [Charity] You've
been most kind.
- Thank you.
- Oh, let us know when
the Pavarotti comes in.
- There's a famous
hotel in Volendam.
♪ Called the Shady Rest ♪
- The Spaander?
Yes, the Spaander.
Christine used to go there
frequently, I recall.
You might try that.
- Thank you.
- But don't eat
the almonds in the bar.
- Good day, Miss Farrel.
Cooper.
- They charge you
10 bucks for them.
- You look a little discouraged.
- Looks like I brought
you on a wild goose chase.
- Oh, there's nothing
to worry about.
- I like geese, oh.
- Christine was
pretty well known
at Lamas's place, I suppose.
- Fernando or Lorenzo?
- Why don't you pick up four
tickets to the affair, huh?
- Four?
You plan to bring a friend.
- Sure, the Joker.
When I play, you see, I
always have one up my sleeve.
- The Joker?
- You'd better reserve
a room for tonight
in a quiet hotel, some
place out of the city.
I'm taking a little
trip to Volendam.
I could get lucky.
- (chuckles) Lucky, get it?
That was a joke. (chuckles)
- Allow me.
- Well, I better get going.
- I'll see you tonight.
- See you at my place,
before your Joker arrives.
- (laughs) Oh, boy, that
kid's got personality plus.
- Picture Picture's
showin' us Holland.
(dreamy music)
- Pannekoeken.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Could you tell me--
- Do you have any dolls--
- Where the Hotel Spaander is?
- Or postcards?
(woman speaking in
foreign language)
(Bryan speaking in
- Thanks a lot.
- Souvenir of Volendam?
- You want me so bad.
- Thank you.
- Damn Secret Super
Jerk, if you ask me.
- Here, give this
to Audrey Hepburn.
- Oh, I'm so embarrassed, you
wore the same thing as me.
(Tom humming)
- Hi, do you know where I
could find some knick-knacks
or curios with kind
of a Holland theme?
- Cheese.
- Oh, somebody
put me up to this.
I hate this.
- Tonight, music box danger.
- Christine Bruder?
Yes, she was one of
my best customers.
She came here almost every night
and brought a whole
crowd with her.
- Well, did you ever happen
to see this man in the group?
- Hey, that's dirty.
- No.
Well, I'm not sure.
No, I don't know him.
There were always
so many for them.
Since they've stopped coming,
this place has
been like a morgue.
- Except for all
those customers.
- Don't you worry, honey.
I think maybe you got
yourself a live one.
Can I use the phone?
- Help yourself.
Marika.
- Now what?
- Ja, Miss Strahl?
- Please help this
gentleman to find the phone.
- Ja, this way, please.
- Don't forget to
come and see me again.
- How could I forget?
- Well, you're a secret agent.
You have a lot on your mind.
- Hey, anywhere I
can go to soak up
the local color?
- There you are.
- I gotta drain
the super dragon.
- Auch, mine god, he's smooth.
- American Embassy,
let me have 233.
- Yes.
- [Bryan] Cooper speaking.
Send the following cable.
American (speaks faintly).
- It's a Franco-American flag.
- [Bryan] Fulton's
presence required
for Bruder heir, stop, Cooper.
- Yes, okay, Mr.
Cooper, right away.
- I've still got it.
(tense music)
- Uh-oh, hey, you're
outta paper there.
- Hmm.
Oh.
Oh well, here goes.
(inhales deeply)
(buzzer sounding)
- I know somebody who borrowed
a pantsuit from Hope Lange.
(Crow growling playfully)
- [Tom] Ooh.
- I hope Mr. Cooper will excuse
me for keeping him waiting.
I just threw on a
little something
to make myself presentable.
- Well, I really don't
mind waiting at all
as long as I think
the results are good.
But I was expecting
Rembrandt 13.
- But it's Miss Farrel
who's receiving tonight.
Please, will you come in.
- Hangin' with Mr. Cooper.
- Oh, you should've seen all
the quaint stuff I saw today.
Boy, that Holland.
- Did you catch anything
in Volendam?
- I think I caught a
little bit of a cold.
- Get ready, he's gonna steal
her cigarette.
- There you go.
- You're not going to
talk about work now.
- I think we're
going to have to.
- Well, Bernice in
the cube next to me
is such a gossip.
- All right, I'll
get you the file.
- Nope.
- Yeah, whew.
- Would you get us
some drinks, please.
- Yep, did it again.
(gentle music)
- I'll take a bourbon.
- Me, too, thanks.
Oh.
- (groans) Tastes like catnip.
- He's putting it
out on the couch.
- Hey, got any magazines?
(Tom humming)
- I'm gonna bend at the
waist someday, I know it.
- A Christmastime slaughterhouse
friend, dime arrears?
- [Joel] He's a slow reader.
- (chuckles) I'm the best
thing in this message.
- [Joel] Man, I'm smug, mm.
(Tom humming)
- Hey, much much
longer ya gonna be?
What, did ya fall in?
Oh.
- [Joel] Anybody
know what's going on?
- Boy, this really ties
into the chewing gum thing.
- Maybe I should
open a curio shop.
(door clicking)
- 'Bout time.
- I wasn't doin' nothin'.
- [Joel] You know,
in that light,
she looks just like Geddy Lee.
(Crow groaning)
- I thought you were
gonna change, what gives?
- [Joel] Should a gentleman
offer a lady a Tiparillo?
- She got tall all of a sudden.
- She can probably really
feel the smoothness now.
Nevermind.
- Boy, she must be getting
paid a lot of money.
- Something intoxicating happens
when Brylcreem and
White Shoulders meet,
you know.
(record scratching)
- Oh, that happens to everyone
now and again.
- [Joel] Oh, he should follow
through on something for once.
- We gotta go.
- This happens very often
in this district.
I'll get a flashlight.
(upbeat music)
- People, places.
Oh, good.
Well, if you've all had a
chance to look over the script,
let's start on page--
- Crow, this better not be
another stupid "Earth
Versus Soup" type
of spec script, buddy.
- Tom, I think you'll
be pleasantly surprised.
I've streamlined, chopped, and
channeled the spy movie genre
to reflect '90s sensibilities.
- Well, you know, Crow, that
sounds really interesting.
- Thank you, Joel.
The market demands it, you know.
Tom, you'll be reading the
part of Sandy Windhamhill,
the good-looking in an
androgynous way super spy
who is in touch with
his feminine side.
I realize I'm asking you
to play against type,
but I think you--
- Gee, that sounds
really stupid, Crow.
I can't foil the evil forces
trying to conquer the world
if I'm a dumb old
sissy britches.
- Wait a minute, Servo.
Let's just give it a chance.
We'll just read Crow's
treatment, okay.
- "The Spy Who Hugged Me."
Joel, you'll be reading a
couple of parts, if you would,
Sandy's love interest,
Holly Affirmations,
and the bad guy, Gary Diabolic.
- For god's sake, man, I wanna
drink martinis in Istanbul
and other glib Bond
malts in Moscow
and drive with my feet while
escaping thugs in Monte Carlo
and meet girls in Ipanema,
the kind of things a
super secret super spy
is supposed to do.
- I support your
owning those feelings.
- Yeah, support this.
- Top of page 12,
Joel, you're Holly.
- Okay.
You understand, Mr. Windhamhill,
that even though we are sharing
a sexual tension between us,
I must kill you.
- Holly, thank you
for being honest.
Let me say that I think
you're a really
terrific, dynamite lady.
But right now, I'm in a
committed relationship
with someone who is
very special to me.
I don't believe this (mutters).
- Okay, Holly pulls a
gun out of her purse,
I'll use my hand, and says,
then you understand, Mr.
Windhamhill, nothing personal.
- Boundaries, Holly,
boundaries, oh.
Crow, I'm supposed to be a man
who leads a life of danger!
- Servo, the only way
around it is through it.
- Oh, brother.
- Okay, let's jump
ahead a few pages.
Sandy has carpooled
with Gary Diabolic
to the World Domination
Headquarters.
And Joel, you're Gary, and
you're going to shame the world
with your specially invented
anti-Bradshaw device.
So top of page 26, and Thomas.
- Okay. (clears throat)
Mr. Diabolic, if you
have a few minutes,
I need to confront you on your
shaming behavior. (scoffs)
- Oh, Mr. Big Windhamhill,
thinks he's going
to save the world.
Well, who do you
think you are, Mister?
- Gary, I feel
you're upset with me.
I know it's not about
me but about issues
in your family of origin.
You have got to be
kidding me, Crow.
- So you think you
know everything,
Mr. Namby Pamby Damby Butt.
Gonna cry now, huh, gonna cry?
- I have to ask you to
respect my boundaries.
- You don't get it, do you,
you stupid moron idiot.
I'm going to control how
people respond to me.
I am going to rule the world!
- Gary, that's
really codependent.
I can't believe I
just said codependent!
That's it, you
completely defiled a
revered film archetype,
and you made me feel
like a total buffoon.
I'm outta here.
- Well, really, only
Tom can make Tom feel
like a total buffoon.
- [Tom] Yeah, bite me.
(buzzer sounding)
- Oh, we movie time.
(group shouting)
(door thudding)
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
- Oh, there he is.
(man grunting)
Oh, good, an action sequence.
- Finally.
- And it's over.
- There he goes, and a
classic Jackie Chan disarm.
- All right, now, who sent ya?
- Oh, right, your bourbon.
- Does this answer
your question?
(tense music)
- You take it easy.
- I take it any way I can.
- He hasn't taught ya.
- Hey, that's my gum!
(man groaning)
- [Joel] Oh, no,
now we'll never know
if Razzles are candy or gum!
- Cyanide.
- It's like poison or somethin'.
- Everybody dies too
quickly in this mess.
I better get rid of him.
- Do you have a garbage
bag or somethin'?
- Whoa, hey, he's a lot
lighter than I thought.
- He's hollow.
- Just set him anywhere.
- Going down, Mr. Interloper?
(water splashing)
- [Joel] Hey, he made the pool.
- It's so convenient to
have a river so close.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, back at it.
(swanky music)
- Amster-damn, I'm good.
- (grumbles) Now,
where were my lips?
Oh, yeah.
- You know, I don't think
I could go back to kissing
after someone just
died in my apartment.
- Yeah, I'd need a while
to pull myself together.
- Sure, a couple of days.
- No, a couple of minutes.
- Well, he seems to be
takin' it all right.
- So does she.
(Crow imitates slurping)
- You still afraid?
- Yes, no, pass.
- No.
- Oh, no, I hope their
chins don't lock.
- Oh, I get it, a
car, a brick road.
(laughs) Drivin' to the.
- Sonny Corleone, watch out.
(Joel imitates rattling)
- Hello, any talent to declare?
- [Joel] Huh, you seem nice.
(suspenseful music)
(Tom humming)
- Plastifa's, a
division of Con-Huge Co.
- Strangely enough, it's an
unfinished furniture place.
(all humming "Get Smart" theme)
- Oh.
- Oh, oh.
- I think you need to
take a rest in Ward E.
(Tom humming)
- Oh, this thing.
- Oh, it tickles. (giggles)
- Oh, that's my zucchini
wrapped in foil.
- [Joel] I'm an extra,
and I still have to
go through this thing.
- There, happy?
Now I'm sterile again.
- Ah, good morning, Mr. Solo.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] All this to get
the the vending machines.
- Looks like he only
has one message.
(curious music)
- Come on, come on!
- Oh, it's Jack Lord again.
- It's Herb from Burger King.
- Could something
please just happen?
- Oh, can't get out now.
- [Joel] Golly, I just
forgot something, okay.
- Don't sit down yet, Alex.
- The chair's still wet.
- Do you realize how many times
you've failed in your mission?
- 12?
Oh, it's rhetorical, shoot.
- [Joel] Does this have
to be an all-staff, sir?
(table beeping)
- Oh, oh, what's that,
didn't know about that.
Would somebody answer
the table, please?
Oh, I'll get it.
- [Joel] Pretty cool,
huh, just had that put in.
- What's it take,
couple of nine-volts?
- [Caller] Professor
Kreuger, I read your report
and I am satisfied with the
results obtained so far.
- Remind your engineers
to use coasters on me.
- But we must make
more rapid progress.
- [Joel] Pick up the
pace, chop, chop.
- [Caller] Dr. Mizimoto.
- Oh, sorry, I wasn't listening.
- [Caller] You have
not yet succeeded
in perfecting a universal
catalyst for Syncron Two.
- [Joel] Well, it's hard.
- [Caller] I'll give
you four days more.
- Starting now, or, oh.
- [Caller] Alex.
- What's with your hair?
- [Caller] A third American
spy is arriving in Amsterdam.
I should be sorry to
have to replace you.
But if you fail me again,
I shall have no choice.
Regarding Christine Bruder,
she has served her purpose.
- That table's
really callin' him
on the carpet.
- All right.
I won't fail you.
- Leonard Cohen at home.
(Joel blowing raspberries)
(all giggling)
- Agent Fulton at your service.
Something I can do for you?
- Yeah, comb your hair.
- You can make out my will.
- First, tell me that
you're glad to see me.
- I'm thrilled to see you.
- Once again, very nicely.
- Here, let me
un-bunch you. (grunts)
- [Joel] Wow, it looks
like they're makin' out
in Peter Brady's room.
- So when's my review?
(phone buzzing)
- Wow, she's responsive.
- That's the phone.
- Hello.
- [Charity] You'd
better come down.
We found Christine.
I'll be in the bar.
- Huh, okay, okay.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
- Business or pleasure.
- It's Rembrandt 13 calling.
- Then it's business.
- Mm, you haven't
seen Rembrandt 13.
- [Joel] She looks like a
white member of The Supremes.
- Who's Comfort?
- A real luscious blonde.
- Oh, that's the Joker.
- Joker?
- Well?
- Looking for Mr. Goodbar?
- She's at the Central Clinic.
They called Lamas, and he
let me know immediately.
- We'd better get there
right away, come on.
- Come on.
- Fashions from the
Lollipop Guild Collection.
- Not bad, huh?
- If you like that
sort of thing.
- Bet that red hair
came out of a bottle.
- Ha, look who's
talking. (belches)
- A martini, please.
- Now, that comes out
of a bottle.
- Two martinis.
- I don't wanna die, help me.
You've got to.
- I don't wanna die.
- Oh, please.
Look, I've got problems, too!
- Anti-Syncron.
Hurry.
- Please, bring me a pizza.
This hospital food's crap.
(Christine groaning)
(curious music)
- Very comforting.
- Yeah, he's got a
good dead-side manner.
- [Lamas] There was
no way to save her.
We don't even know
what killed her.
- Gum?
- Well, there's some things
that I have to attend to,
that I have to do, the things.
Bye.
- Science!
- Yes, what have you come for?
- Pencils?
- Christine is dead.
You killed her by
refusing her the antidote.
After all she had done for you,
and the same will happen to me.
- You seem upset.
- Yes, it could.
Super Dragon is
not yet eliminated.
- [Group] Ew.
- Because you failed.
- I don't want to kill anybody.
Until now, I've done
everything for you,
even against my will.
You have got to
keep your promise
and free me from this drug.
- Please.
- Hey, how'd they do that?
(Charity speaking faintly)
- Impressionable.
- They're both doin'
Shelley Berman routines.
- I saw that man again.
Yes, Lamas.
- What's that lump
on his chest?
- So you followed him?
- You don't wanna know.
- Of course,
but he managed to get away.
- I'm not that good
at following yet.
- His being at the
clinic makes me believe
that this girl didn't
die a natural death.
What's more, they're going
to bury her tomorrow.
- Don't that beat all.
- They're a little bit too much
in a hurry, don't you think?
- Well, maybe we'll
beat them to it.
- [Joel] Looks great
from this angle.
- I think I'll take a look
around that clinic tonight.
- Tell them your volley ball
practice is running late.
- The service entrance
is Lijkenkelder 16.
- Yes, I think I can
find that all right.
You're always right on the ball,
aren't ya, sweetheart, huh?
- Yes, I'm in a Howard Johnson.
- (chuckles) God, I'm good.
- [Joel] Oh, terrific,
this guy's back.
- (clears throat) Excuse me,
sir, where are you going?
Sir, I have to stamp
your hand, sir.
Sir.
- Could you explain again
why I do all the work?
- This is too easy.
- Then what took you so long?
- [Joel] Hey, why can't
you ever support me?
- Have a good time.
- I'm gonna make the
deposit, I'll be right back.
- [Joel] Hmm, 200 a month
plus utilities, huh?
(tense music)
- A Screen Gems presentation.
- The other apartments
I've snooped around
are much nicer than this.
(Tom humming)
- Wow, this is a
swingin' boiler room.
- Yeah, it's cool.
- Dig it.
(Tom scatting)
- Oh, (laughs) there
it is, the (mumbles).
(Tom humming)
- Hooray, I'm Superclown!
(men grunting)
- Ooh, ooh.
- I paid to see
the Leichenkeller,
and I'm not leaving 'til I do.
- Jim West.
- Baby Face, I'm being
beat up by longshoremen.
- Well, this isn't bad, we'll
be home in time, hey, oh.
- This looks like the end
of Romancing the Stone.
It's not funny, I'm
just pointing it out.
- Looks like a
Crosby family outing.
- Man, whatever Liechenkeller
is, it must be pretty good.
- Took the Nestea
Plunge. (speaks faintly)
(tense music)
- [Joel] It was my
punch, you know.
- Yeah, well, I made him woozy.
- [Joel] Ooh, he needs a
shovel-proof vest there.
- Oh, great.
- Taken care of the one outside.
- Good, now we'd
better get moving.
- Yes, it's Lech Walesa
and Billy Pilgrim.
- Ha, fooled ya!
(stomp thudding)
Ooh, maybe not.
- Stay still.
- Boy, it's a good thing
that 24-hour mortuary
is just around the corner.
- Now, give me a hand with this.
(group cheering)
- Yay, woo.
- Boy, he sure is smooth, boss.
- Hey, he fits.
Last time, we has
to cut the feet off.
Screw the lid down.
- [Joel] If you wanna
lock in deadness.
- His chin looks
like a Parker House roll.
(men speaking faintly)
(men laughing)
- I'm not dead yet.
Hey, I'm feelin' better.
- [Joel] You know, some
day we should all go in
and buy a Makita.
- Guys, this isn't funny.
Man, I hate Hell Week.
- You better telephone the boss.
- Right.
- Borrow me a quarter.
- [Joel] Hey, he's gonna show
himself a Linda Hunt movie.
- Good morning, Mr. Phelps,
'orning, Mr. Phelps,
'orning, Mr. Phel.
- Hello?
This is Valiki.
- It's a great day
at Tires Plus.
- He's ready for you.
Yeah, ready for the burial.
What?
Okay, good idea, right, boss.
- (chuckles) Guy's
actually pretty funny.
- Okay, guys, I give.
Fun's over, guys, fun's over.
- What are you doin'?
- The boss has had
a brilliant idea
of dropping it into you canal,
where it's gonna disappear
without leavin' a trace.
(men chuckling)
- I heard that, it's not funny.
- [Thug] It'll all
be over in an hour.
- Guys, guys, it's
really hot in here.
Oh, screw ya then.
(tense music)
- I'm gonna time
how long I live.
That'll show 'em.
- One--
- Mississippi.
- Hour.
- Father.
(breath rasping)
- Hey, what do ya know,
something's connectin' with
somethin' else in the film.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Okay, take that end.
- Lift with the
legs, good, good.
- Oh, I get it, he's
gonna lower his metabolism
like James Coburn did
in "In Like Flint."
(Tom humming "Funeral March")
- Come on, guys,
let's do the song.
(Tim humming "Funeral March")
Come on.
- Okay, okay, lean
your end a little.
There you go, grab that end.
(Tom groaning)
Okay, good, good, good.
- Oh, man, he's...
- [Joel] You know, you
find yourself doin'
the weirdest things
in this business.
- (laughs) Ain't it the truth.
- Right in the lake.
- Oh, and this guy's dead.
We don't gotta
buy him no ticket.
- But there was no monster.
- Here at Gorton's of
Gloucester, we bury
our corpses fresh.
- Never expected this to happen.
- Oh, you mean he's still alive?
Wow.
- Hey, what's he doin'?
Stop that.
- That's bad.
- Naughty.
♪ Old Dutch, the snappy chip ♪
♪ Crispy, crunchy eatin' ♪
- Windmills were
held stationary today
in tribute to the death of
Secret Agent Super Dragon.
- [Joel] They are so
incredibly in Holland, man.
- Well, they
shouldn't have taken
the harbor excursion
boat to do this.
- (sniffs) We commit
the body to the deep.
Dump 'im!
- Okay, boys.
There he goes.
- Ha, fooled ya,
I wasn't breathe,
whoa, whoa, just filled
the lungs up with water.
(chuckles) I'm in for it now.
Didn't wanna do that.
- Bon voyage.
- Charlie Brown.
(unsettling music)
- (yawns) I'm tired.
I think I'll sleep
with the fishes.
- Ouch, owie.
- Only way he could foil us is
if he reduced his breathing.
- Aw, don't even think about
him doin' that.
- Yeah, you're right.
Let's go have a Grolsch.
- Ah, sure, sounds good.
(upbeat music)
(tense music)
♪ Somewhere ♪
♪ Beyond the sea ♪
- At least he has his cash card.
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Conrad Pooh and
his inflatable knees.
♪ Here's George Jetson ♪
- I see yer white belly!
(blade buzzing)
- Oh, no, I'll get
it from the inside.
Ow!
- [Joel] Oh, this must be
in the Brookstone
Hard-to-Find Tool Catalog.
(blade buzzing)
- Ah!
- Oh, that noise.
- Oh.
- Fork on a plate.
- Free, it's me.
(coughs) What's my
time on this one?
Oof.
- They're doing all this
in front of a Starving
Artist painting.
- Did you sleep well, Bryan?
- [Joel] Oh, very
frigging funny,
Tom Wicker.
- The bed was bit damp.
And the service was lousy.
But it could have
been a lot worse
if it hadn't been for your help.
- And now everybody
thinks we're dead.
- That might work out
better than you'd think.
- (chuckles) Thanks, Peanut.
- April 11th, dear
diary, he's dead.
I can now love Stan.
Finally came to
terms with the hair.
Oh, and I found the
perfect clown suit
to wear around the house.
- Coleman to Bryan Cooper,
conditions in Fremont worse,
hundreds of students taken
to psychiatric clinic, stop.
- Don't stop.
- So far, impossible to--
- Stop.
- Halt sickness progress,
stop.
Ming vases found Ross home,
false and fabricated with
unknown substance, stop.
Absolutely urgent, learn
drug formula for antidote.
- Is it a humorous antidote?
- Yes.
(group chuckling)
- Hey, anybody wanna
go bowlin', somethin'?
- [Christine] I don't
wanna die, help me.
You've got to, please.
- Mary had (imitates
static crackling)
a little lamb.
- Anti-Syncron.
- Its fleece--
- Hurry. (groans)
- [Joel] Hey, it's Donna Summer.
- Oh.
- What do you know?
- Oh, he uses his reel-to-reel
to light his cigarette.
- Anti-Syncron,
that's the antidote.
Anti-Syncron.
Christine was drugged
by the same drug
the kids in Fremont got.
- But who's got
this Anti-Syncron?
- Yeah, let's drop this
and bowl a few frames.
- This should tell us.
Eight.
Four.
- And huzzah, it's gone.
- Three.
- Two.
Zero, dial it.
- Me?
- Yeah, go ahead.
We're supposed to be dead.
- Who do I ask for?
- Just whoever answers is fine.
- Charity Farrel.
- And then just hang up quick.
- I think it might really help
if they'd let us in on
the plot, don't you think?
- Could you stand a
little closer, please?
- She's modeling the Florence
Henderson collection, I see.
(machine buzzing)
- [Joel] Your pen
is ringing, sir.
- My table's a guy, my
pen is a phone, I'm nuts!
- Yes, who's there?
- [Comfort] I'd like to speak
to Charity Farrel, please.
- It's an office.
Why does he have to
disguise the phone?
- There isn't anyone
here called Charity.
You have the wrong number.
- [Joel] Am I on speaker pen?
- Okay, now call Lamas's place.
Use the introduction
we agreed upon.
Call.
Three.
Six.
- Tell anybody about my pen,
and I'll have to kill you.
- Did you give her this number?
- No, never.
(phone ringing)
- Answer the chafing dish.
- Yes?
- It's a great day
at House of Art.
- Mr. Lamas's house.
Comfort Denbe.
Tell me.
- Oh, that's for me.
I'll take it on the
pencil sharpener.
- Yes.
- Yes, yes, I'm wearing
a sleeveless tank top.
- Yes.
Just a moment, please.
- Run!
Oh, oh, you're right there.
- Comfort Denbe says
her American friends,
Cooper and the other one,
promised her an
invitation to the auction
and now she can't
find them anywhere.
- Oh, and friends are
visiting from Europe.
- Good morning, yes.
- Yes.
- Yes, my secretary
mentioned it.
- Yes, just a burgundy
sweater with a tie.
- Very well, I'll send
you an invitation.
Hotel Ruutek.
Splendid, I'm looking
forward to it.
I think you'll like
our entertainment.
So, goodbye.
- [Joel] That's how ya
handle a super dragon.
- Our friend is
in for a surprise.
Only, after we learn
where she got that number.
(Tom laughing maniacally)
- Well, from here
on out, sweetheart,
I'm afraid they're gonna
put the finger on you.
- Like a cigarette, boss?
- You seem to be
the only surviving American
agent who knows who Lamas is.
- Thanks a lot.
- Yeah, but you'll have us
two covering you from behind.
- [Joel] Aw, you've
been in prison too long.
- In other words, I
have to serve as bait.
- That's right,
and I hope you try
and be a very attractive bait.
- I'll try.
- Miss Collagen Lips.
(lighthearted music)
- Welcome to the Fred
Mertz Mystery Cafe.
- See, they told me
it was a costume ball.
That's why I--
♪ Around the world in 80 days ♪
(Tom humming)
See, really, they told
me it was a costume ball.
Boy, aren't I the
perfect ass? (laughs)
- Hey, looks like it's
snowin' upstairs. (chuckles)
- One word, Ben: plastics.
- Hey, someone's
gotta make a keg run.
- Okay, we'll just shoot
down to Belgium, man.
They're open later.
- Yeah, get the French
ambassador to go.
- Oh, no, that wild
man Rainier wants
to put the new riders on again.
- [Tom] Woo.
- [Joel] Hey, come on.
Hey, everybody stay
outta my parents' room.
Come on.
- [Auctioneer] 8,000 once.
8,000 twice.
Sold for 8,000 florins.
- She pulled in a good price.
- [Crow And Tom] Mm-hmm.
- I never knew that
Chinese Ming vases
could bring such a high price.
- It's a game of vanity
for a worthy cause.
- [Auctioneer] Would
you step here, sir.
- Number 73, a date with
Prince Philip, wants Philip.
(guests chattering faintly)
- Mm, sorry, sir,
TeleCheck says no way.
- Would you please.
- Beautiful vases,
authentic Ming.
- Yeah, just like
the ones in Fremont.
- Oh, that was low.
- Have you noticed how all
four vases have been bought
by men in silver masks.
- Don't you hate that?
- You're a fortunate man.
- Thank you.
- Find out where
he's going, huh.
- Got a big old
hole in his head.
- Now, ladies and gentlemen,
we offer the
next-to-last Ming vase.
The artist who spends his
life in creating these
has evidently excelled himself
in this allegory of spring.
- How much?
- Starting price,
a mere 3,000 florins.
- All right then, 2,000.
- 3,500.
- 5,000.
- 5,500.
- I've got some lupins.
- Nine.
- Seven, I bid.
- 8,000, I bid.
- Eight-five, I bid.
- 9,000.
- [Joel] They're all dressed
as Mexican wrestlers.
- El Santo.
(gentle music)
- You know, he should put
eye holes in that thing.
- Oh, this is the nicest
voting booth I've seen.
Oh, and it feels
good, too, lookit.
- [Joel] Time to go.
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
(Tom humming)
- Hey Joel, I've got
a pretty good handle
on what's cool, right?
- That's right, you do.
- Ha!
- And your average spy movie--
- Sorry.
Is generally pretty
high on the cool scale?
- Oh, absolutely.
There's nothing cooler than
being a secret agent super spy.
- Well, then would say
that this guy, while lame,
is typical of most guys
in most spy movies?
- Yeah, well, yeah.
- Then I have a question.
- I was hoping this
was headed somewhere.
- How come this guy keeps
saying confusing stuff?
Like, the time he gets jumped,
which is obviously a bad thing,
he said, "They gave me
a real warm reception."
- Oh, well, they all go to
Super Secret Spy School.
That's where they learn to
hone their precise skills,
like how to
simultaneously attract
and repel the opposite sex,
the virtues of doing
espionage in Monte Carlo
as opposed to Little
Chute, Wisconsin,
what makes turtlenecks
so darn cool.
And most importantly,
they take a course
called Post-Kill Puns.
And that's where you
learn to say things like,
we went for a little swim,
which means they
tried to drown me.
- Oh, now, that's a cool class.
Tell me more.
- Yeah, sure.
Oh, yeah, they've got one
hard-and-fast rule there
is you can kill anyone
unless you got a pun.
Shooting someone is out.
Instead, it'd be more
apropos to, like,
push someone into the
lion's den and say,
he went out for a bite.
- Oh.
- See?
- Or run someone over with
a steamroller and say,
he was pressed for time.
- Right, like that.
- Or how about, push
a gal out of a plane,
and then say, oh,
she just stepped out.
- Right, and then there's
always the classic,
I was all tied up, which means--
- [All] I was all tied up.
- Right.
(bots laughing)
- You know, guys, I just
realized that being a spy
is one of the only times when
a pun is actually acceptable.
- Yeah, ironically,
death actually softens
the blow of the pun.
- True.
- You know, I think I'd
like to be a secret agent
just for the pun of it. (laughs)
- Oh, Tom, I'm gonna rip your
inoperable little arms off
and jettison them into space.
- Oh, Crow, you're so disarming.
- D'oh!
Let me at 'im, let
me at 'im. (growls)
- We'll be right back.
- I really gotta hand
it to you. (laughs)
- That's it, that--
- You're goin' out
on a limb. (laughs)
(upbeat music)
- Oh.
- Boy, we're having
thumb pun, huh?
- Geez.
- Oh, just watch the movie.
- Hmm, here, I'll
get my own tip.
- Oh, the guy's
got Snoopy checks.
- Let's see what
else, a harmonica?
I just rolled Toots Thielemans.
- [Joel] Oh no, he's
gonna wheelbarrow him.
- Now he's a fajita.
(bots chuckling)
- Oh, boy, huh.
You know, there's an
episode of Skinny and Fatty
that's just like this.
- [Joel] Hey, real comfortable
confessional suite.
Feels good, too.
(doors whooshing)
- Hey, that was a lucky guess.
- Oh, come in, we were just
about to float the table.
- (speaks in foreign language)
Monsieur, place your bet.
(tense music)
- Hey, he's
disguising his throat
- Oh boy, this has all the
markings of a Clay Shaw party.
Woo-hoo.
(Tom harmonizing)
- Ladies and gentlemen,
Sandler and Young!
(Joel imitating crowd cheering)
- [Joel] The gentlemen now
retire to the back room
to play Racko.
- Murray, use a coaster.
- Earth.
- Luna.
- Pluto.
- [Joel] Goofy.
Scrooge McDuck.
- Mars.
- Saturn.
- Jupiter.
- Secret Agent Super Dragon
in a deadly game of
Hungry Hungry Hippo.
- And this one,
I don't think I need to
tell you guys what that is.
- [Lamas] I'm glad to
see you, gentlemen.
- [Group] Charmed.
- [Joel] The meeting of the
Society of Guys Who Can Make a W
will now begin.
- Watch your fingers, guys.
- Oh, I love it when
the table talks.
This is great, watch
this, watch it, watch.
- The little town of--
- [Group] Bethlehem.
- Fremont has witnessed the
success of our experiment.
- I must impress upon you--
- Me?
- I importance of this
success for us all.
- Come on, boss, can't
the table talk now.
- You will also be glad to learn
that we have
liquified Syncron Two.
- Lick-a-fied.
- This means that
our opportunities of
administering it are limitless.
I'll give you an example.
- I'll perform a puppet
show to demonstrate.
(Tom gasps)
- The Bogart.
- Oh, my god.
- It is a Bogart.
- That is not my Bogart.
- [Tom] You are looking
directly into room 212.
(Crow pants)
- And now your General
Cinema feature presentation.
(Tom humming)
- [Joel] Hi.
- [Tom] Hey, everybody, look
at the guys in the mirror.
- [Auctioneer] And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
before the piece de
resistance of the evening,
Senor Lamas invites all of you
to drink to the success
of this benefit auction.
- And really drink,
down 'em, shooters.
- [Tom And Crow] Ooh!
- [Tom] "Petticoat Junction."
(group harmonizing)
- [Joel] Cigars,
cigarettes, Tiparillos?
- Blonde on blonde
on blonde on blonde.
- It's the Edie Adams gang.
- Ooh.
- In the champagne, there
is a carefully balanced dose
of Syncron Two.
- [Joel] That makes
your hair bouncy, right?
- Just enough of it to amuse us.
In half an hour, they
will remember nothing.
- In another half an hour,
they're be hungry for Chinese.
- Ooh, wow, so this is
what the other half does.
(crowd chattering)
(crowd laughing)
(Tom imitating liquid glugging)
- Thank you, here we go.
- It's booze call.
- Here's to those
big brown eyes.
- [Tom] Yeah, here's
to your death, big guy.
(high-pitched beeping)
- Waitress, there's a
squeeze toy in my drink.
- Miss, miss, I just
remembered, I don't drink.
- Whoa, close one.
- And now the most precious
treasure of the collection.
The magnificent Lute
Player by Franz Hals.
I ask you, ladies and gentlemen,
to open the bidding
at 1,500,000 florins.
- [Bidder] Two million.
- Four!
- Ah, two million.
I'm offered two million once,
two million twice, and--
- [Bidder] Three million.
- I'll offer you 3 1/2.
- [Auctioneer]
Anyone to top 3 1/2?
- Six million.
- A bajillion!
- A kazillion jillion
upteen bernillion!
- That's what I consider
a personal insult!
- Hi.
- Oh, yeah?
- Teach you a lesson.
- Oh, that, sir, I
consider a personal punch.
- Oh, they've been given a drink
that turns them into Shriners.
- Oh, how horrible.
- Will you look at that?
(crowd chattering)
(crowd laughing)
- Hey, everybody, let's boink.
- It's a good night at Au Bar.
- Ah, Louis XIV, good one.
That's two or three mil.
(punch cracking)
- They're all just
behaving like animals.
- [Joel] Hey, bring
back the funny pictures.
- What you have seen
is only an example
of the efficiency
of Syncron Two.
Whenever we choose to use it,
then victory will be ours.
- Victory over what?
- Yes, gentlemen, the
victory will indeed be ours.
- Ours the victory will be.
- We are going to change
the course of human life.
The antidote, Anti-Syncron, is
known to us and to us alone.
- Oh, and I told my brother,
but he said he
wouldn't tell anyone.
- And with it, we shall
gain world mastery.
Foreign agents have
tried to stop us,
notably, the invincible
Super Dragon.
They have been killed.
The false Ming vases are
now in our possession.
The vases have been sent here
from our factories in India.
- [Joel] We have
factories in India?
- The drug is mixed
with the porcelain
in such a way that no
one could ever detect it.
- But still, it's
delicious and low cal.
- In six of them, there is a
sufficient quantity of the drug
to bring to a conclusion the
first phase of the operation.
(crowd shouting)
- [Joel] Phase one:
swingin' '60s style party.
- Woo-hoo.
- You're on.
- Oh, nothing, nothing.
- That's odd, they're
playin' Twister,
but there ain't
no Twister board.
- Doris Day, no!
(tense music)
- It's Serena.
- I'll fix that, Samantha.
(imitates chiming)
- Hello, I am Louis Jourdan.
I turn like you, I
walk, I have a gun,
and still I am Louis Jourdan.
Cover me while I
hit the snack table.
- I'm Louis Jourdan.
- Don't make a sound.
Get moving.
- [Joel] Peep.
- Brilliant, our compliments.
- Mother always calls during
these meetings, sorry.
- I can at last to you
that Professor Kreuger
has been able to find a--
- Oh, it left.
- And tomorrow
we will have it.
Gentlemen, await instructions.
- [Joel] Can I ask why
we're at this meeting?
- We will adjourn.
- Let's get some of that
kooky champagne, huh.
(man groaning)
- Ah, criminy, Dave's doin' his
human cake roll thing again.
You gotta jump on him
and squirt the jelly out.
- I'm a naughty
little cheesy blintz.
- Cut it out, Dave.
- Get Lamas.
- Get to the embassy right
away, contact Coleman.
The Ming vases--
- Okay.
- Are leaving tonight.
- I can do that.
- They must be stopped,
and the names and addresses--
- All right, mm-hmm.
- Of all the buyers
investigated.
- Uh-huh, go on.
- I'll take care of Comfort.
You get going instead.
- Oh, oh, yeah.
- [Baby Face] Okay.
(upbeat music)
- Hi, where you goin',
what are you doin'?
Just wanna walk with you is all.
Nice dress.
- [Bryan] Comfort?
- [Joel] Comfort me.
(lighthearted music)
(Comfort giggling)
- Whoa, those guys are
still hopped up on vase.
- Geez, it was just a case
of mistaken identity, sorry.
Heck of a ride, huh, oof.
- Well, at least
his vicious beating
has a cool accompaniment.
- [Tom] This'll teach
ya to make blintzes
outta super criminals. (grunts)
- Now, let's begin
with Lamas's number.
- Fernando or Lorenzo?
- I'd like to know how
you got hold of it.
- But I've told
you, it was Cooper.
(slap cracking)
(Comfort gasping)
- [Group] Boo!
- The dead don't talk.
- You see this place
around quittin' time.
- You are very beautiful.
- She's sure wearin'
a funny bathing suit.
And it would be a pity to
have to put you in our tub.
- For you see, the Mr. Bubble
may give you a
urinary infection.
- Tell me, have you ever
had a bath in electricity?
- Well, once I saw a
bear eating a donut.
(electricity sizzling)
- Hey, George Wendt.
- Wendt where?
Ha, another one, thank you.
- D'oh, Servo.
(punch cracking)
♪ Da-da da-dump ♪
- This is like "The Quiet Man,"
only it takes place in
a mansion in Holland
with a couple of spies.
- Now, Gary, this
is the last time
you're going to come home late.
(men grunting)
- [Joel] Hey, he's got him in
a Secret Agent Full Dragon.
(suspenseful music)
- Bocephus, what's
he doin' here?
- All right.
Time to play the little
blintz game, Mister.
- [Charity] Stop.
- You boys stop
roughhousing in there.
- I want him alive.
I thought you were
10 feet under, Bryan.
- 10 feet under Bryan?
- Well, you were wrong.
- Dennis James?
- Like always.
- Not anymore.
Hands up.
- Now Simon says put 'em down.
- Let's talk.
- See, she wants
me alive, told you.
You would have gotten
into a lot of trouble.
What?
(tense music)
- Oh, come to think of it, I
did have a bath like that once.
Thanks, though.
- [Alex] This ought to
refresh your memory.
- And your pores.
- Coward.
- Oh, all of a sudden
they're at the Alamo.
(machine clicking)
- [Comfort] (gasps)
You'll pay for this.
They'll get even with you.
- Gee, could I have that cell?
(gun banging)
- Ooh, right in the cummerbund.
- [Joel] I'm with a client.
Sir, we don't take walk-ins.
(gun banging)
(Charity gasps)
Oh!
(gun banging)
- Whoa-we-ho.
(Charity groaning)
- It's my roomate's dress.
- Wait, wait, wait, who's alive?
Let's count off here.
(mournful music)
- [Joel] Hey, it's not my gun.
Check the powder
burns, I didn't do it.
(Charity gasps)
- Hmm, one last
kiss would be nice.
- The antidote.
- You've got a big ball
of wax in there.
- Alex knows where it is.
He must have it.
Everything depends on it.
- Oh, that's all right,
it's all right now.
Don't speak anymore,
don't speak anymore.
- [Joel] All right,
you shot me, you jerk.
- I can't believe
I ever liked you.
- I couldn't help myself--
- I ate the last Frusen Gladje.
- It was the drugs.
- I know.
I always knew.
- [Joel] I knew it was the drug.
Yes, it was the drug, I knew it.
- You know what, it'd be
really bad if you died
while I was kissing
you right now.
Now, how does that make me feel?
Geez.
- He had to get every last
drop of love outta her.
- [Joel] Well, I
could still hug her.
That's not that weird, is it?
- No.
- Dead, huh?
Well, best untie the
other one. (chuckles)
- (sighs) I just let myself out.
- The haunting Herb
Alpert death theme,
here on the Music of Your Life.
- Hey, now, wait a second.
Two wrongs aren't
gonna make a right.
- [Joel] Yeah, there.
- Well, I'll do the honors.
- Super Dragon worked the
deep fryers at Arby's.
He knows what he's doin'.
- [Joel] They're
gonna rust-proof him.
- Now would you
guys scrub my back.
Oh, and there's a bottle
of Sardo someplace.
- Well.
- Well?
- What do you have
to say to me, huh?
- I've got nothing to say.
Just go to hell!
- That's very rude of you.
Comfort, teach him some manners.
- Well, the small fork
is for the shrimp,
and keep your head
below the queen.
(electricity sizzling)
- You won't make me talk.
- All right.
- This will be a
shocking experience.
Watts for dinner? (laughs)
- Oh, Servo.
- [Joel] Oh, I love it.
Increase the amps, come on.
(Alex shouts)
- You have a
beautiful voice, Alex.
Have you ever thought
about going on the stage?
- You'll both die for this.
- Although I was in "Oliver!"
on senior sketch night.
I had this little--
(electricity sizzling)
(Alex shouting)
- Make her stop and I'll talk.
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, it's Frank the
bodyguard's apartment.
- What, what, are they
in Filene's Basement
all of a sudden?
- Geez, he should put a
fence around that thing.
He might run into problems when
he has a lot of people over.
They could get their head
crushed in or something.
- [Joel] Oh, that's
still workin' anyway.
I haven't been home in a while.
- Used to have handles on
it, you could just open it.
It was actually more convenient.
(detector beeping)
Same deal here pretty much,
more for show, really.
I can get you one if want one.
- Oh.
- [Joel] Boy, you're really
proud of that clay squirrel,
aren't ya?
- [Bryan] I'm very
happy to see you again.
- I was being facetious.
- Can I give you hand?
- Why, sure, you can help us.
(gun banging)
Ooh!
- [Joel] Just come
right in, Ray.
- The set's gonna
give you a hand.
(Lamas laughing)
- He was the only one left
who could tell you the formula
for the Anti-Syncron.
- Did it have
mushroom soup in it?
- So you mission has failed,
Cooper, failed totally.
As for me, I couldn't kill
you now even if I wanted to.
- [Joel] This is my
head shot, you know.
(Lamas grunting)
(Lamas gasping)
- You hear that, Lizabeth?
I'm comin' to join you, honey!
- I don't need the formula.
- We're the silver dragon.
- I already photographed it
in your office with this camera.
Look, see.
Huh, huh?
- So you're killing
yourself for nothing.
Nyah-nyah-nyah nyah-nyah nyah.
- [Joel] What a jerk, he just
wanted to get the guy's goat
right before he died.
- The boys in Fremont
are saved.
And there's loads of
declarations pouring in for you.
We're just waiting
for you to get back.
- [Bryan] Yeah, well,
when are you expecting me?
- Senator Hollings,
get off the line.
- Right away, of course.
- [Bryan] Well, don't
hold your breath.
- What?
I don't understand.
- Yeah, you heard me all right.
I'm taking a little vacation.
- [Comfort] Why?
- Why?
- I had the time comin'.
- Holland is
beautiful in the fall.
- [Comfort] What
about Baby Face?
- Oh, with Baby Face?
- He's beautiful any time.
- Yeah, I know,
I've gotta send him
right back to Sing Sing.
But I'm afraid I can't
do that right now.
He seems to be very, very busy
absorbing the local color.
- [Joel] Appears he's
adopted a Dutch family.
- Now, listen, you made
a deal with Coleman
to bring him back now.
You can't break your word, a
deal is a deal, do you hear!
Now, you and Baby Face
get on the first plane--
- Flint!
(Comfort speaking faintly)
- Well, I'm very sorry,
but there's nothing
I can do about that.
- [Comfort] Bryan!
Are you listening to me?
- Who, me?
(Tom imitates turkey gobbling)
I'm gonna be very busy, too,
studying the local customs.
- [Joel] How about a little
Dutch treat, huh? (chuckles)
- [Crow] At least the
movie had a good payoff.
- Yeah.
(machinery clanging)
(metal creaking)
Okay, no, no, no.
It's very simple.
- Simple.
- Secret--
- Secret simple.
- Agent--
- Agenting.
- Super Dragon.
- Secret super dragon
lady thing, oh.
- All right, knock it
off, you mutton heads.
We gotta do that
supervillain conference call
with Dr. Forrester.
- Supervillain
deal, oh, forget it.
- Coming, Your Surliness.
♪ Sing a-sing a-sing ♪
Oh, hi, Joel.
Dr. Forrester'll be
with you in one minute.
- Ah, Mr. Robinson, why don't
you introduce your colleagues?
- Well, sir, it's pretty
much the same colleagues
as I always have, Tom
Servo, Crow T. Robot.
Gypsy couldn't make it.
- [Crow And Tom] Hi.
- Well, thank you
for coming by today.
Our topic is supervillains.
And I think I'd like to open
it up to question and answer.
Well, thank you Frank.
- Whatever.
- Could I get some cream?
- No.
- Great.
Joel?
- Well, I think the question
our field reps asked most
at this week's movie meeting was
why the supervillain
in today's film failed
to make any kind
of an impression.
Gentlemen?
- Right, right.
- Pretty much, yep.
- No impression at all.
- Ah, very good.
Well, perhaps one reason why
this supervillain failed,
and I believe the 1971
Dr. Noah monograph
will back me up here,
is that he did not
possess a strange
or rare animal.
I can't be too
strong on this point.
Either four legs or two,
every supervillain
must have an animal.
Frank, I believe
you had a question.
- Oh, oh, yeah.
Eagerly, I've always thought
it would be easy and fun
to start up a
supervillain franchise.
Is that true?
- Ah, excellent
question, very good.
No.
No, it is not easy
to set up a
supervillain franchise.
You see, today's
supervillain is, in essence,
the small business
owner of his franchise.
He does the purchasing,
the hiring, the firing,
plus must maintain medical
and dental and benefits
for an unstable and terribly
dishonest group of henchmen.
But if you are dedicated
and are not afraid of
a little hard work,
then you'll find that the
field of super-villainry
can be very rewarding indeed.
Yes, next question.
- Well, the only thing
we wanted to ask,
and I think we're all in
agreement on this, is--
- [All] What do you think, sirs?
- Good question.
Push the button, Frank.
(switch clicking)
(video whooshing)
What the, hey!
(dramatic music)
(lighthearted music)
(men grunting)
- [Announcer] This has
been a presentation
from Comedy Central.